A Guide to the Papers of The World Affairs Council of Hampton Roads 1968-2000
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- 2000s
  - Programs And Events
    - Joseph F. Bouchard, PhD, Executive Director of the Center for Homeland Security and Defense (CHSD) January 18, 2005 (Box-folder 34:2)
    - Great Decisions 2005 (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Ambassador Michael G. Kozak, Acting Assistant Secretary, Bureau of Democracy, Human Rights and Labor February 17, 2005 (Box-folder 34:4)
    - World Affairs Councils of America Leadership Mission Bulletin - Egypt February 20-27, 2005 (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Lennart Sacredeus, Former Member of the European Parliament March 16, 2005 (Box-folder 34:6)
    - Michael Krepon, Co-Founder and President Emeritus of the Stimson Center-Lieutenant General Daniel Leaf, Vice Commander of the Air Force Space Command May 10, 2005 (Box-folder 34:7)
    - World Quest 2005 (Box-folder 34:8)
    - World Affairs Councils of America Leadership Mission Bulletin - Tunisia February 5-12, 2006 (Box-folder 34:9)
    - Dr. Mitchell B. Reiss, U.S. Special Envoy to Northern Ireland March 2, 2006 (Box-folder 34:10)
    - Dr. Jeffrey Bader, Director of the China Initiative and Senior Fellow at the Brookings Institute March 22, 2006 (Box-folder 34:11)
    - His Excellency Mohamed Nejib Hachana, Ambassador of Tunisia to the United States- Mr. Oussama Romdhani, Director General, Tunisian External Communication Agency (ATCE) March 29, 2006 (Box-folder 34:12)
    - World Affairs Councils of America Leadership Mission Bulletin - Taiwan April 23- 29, 2006 (Box-folder 34:13)
    - His Excellency Euripides Evriviades, Ambassador of Cyprus to the United States May 11, 2006 (Box-folder 34:14)
    - Margaret McGuinness, University of Missouri Law School & June 9, 2006 - Dr. Edward Oldfield, Eastern Virginia Medical School June 2, 2006 (Box-folder 34:15)
    - Programs 2005-2007 (Box-folder 34:16)
    - Passed Annual Conferences (I) undated (Box-folder 34:17)
    - Passed Annual Conferences (II) undated (Box-folder 34:18)
  - Finance
    - AMSEC Invoices 2004-2005 (Box-folder 34:19)
    - AMSEC Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2005-2006 (Box-folder 34:20)
    - AT&T Info 2004-2005 (Box-folder 34:21)
    - Audit 2000-2001 2000-2001 (Box-folder 34:22)
    - Audit 2002-2003 (Box-folder 34:23)
    - Audit 2003-2004 (Box-folder 34:24)
    - Audit 2005 (Box-folder 35:1)
    - Bank Card 2003-2005 (Box-folder 35:2)
    - Bank of America Certificates of Deposit 2004 (Box-folder 35:3)
    - Bank Statements 2004 (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Bank Statements 2005 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Bank Statements 2006 (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Boise Cascade Office Products Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2001 (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Boise Office Max 2003-2004 (Box-folder 35:8)
    - Brand Fuel Invoices 2006 (Box-folder 35:9)
    - Budget 2002-2003 (Box-folder 35:10)
    - Check Requests 2004 (Box-folder 35:11)
    - Check Requests 2004-2005 (Box-folder 35:12)
    - Check Requests 2005-2006 (Box-folder 35:13)
    - Checks/Invoices 2000 (Box-folder 35:14)
    - COG Application 2002-2003 (Box-folder 35:15)
    - COG Application 2003-2004 (Box-folder 35:16)
    - Deposits 2000-2001 (Box-folder 35:17)
    - Deposits 2001-2002 (Box-folder 35:18)
    - Deposits 2004 -2005 (Box-folder 36:1)
    - Deposits 2005-2006 (Box-folder 36:2)
    - Deposits and Statements January 2003- June 2003 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - Deposits and Statements July 2002- December 2002 (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Deposits and Statements July 2003- January 2004 (Box-folder 36:5)
    - Deposits and Statements July 2003- June 2004 (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Deposits April- June 2005 (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Deposits January - June 2006 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - Deposits January - May 2004 (Box-folder 37:2)
    - Deposits August-December 2003 (Box-folder 37:3)
    - Deposits July- December 2005 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Deposits June October 2004 (Box-folder 37:5)
    - Deposits November 2004- March 2005 (Box-folder 37:6)
    - Dues Calculation Sheets 1997-2003 (Box-folder 37:7)
    - Employee Payments 1998-2000 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - Employer Tax Returns 2002-2005 (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Expenses 2004-2005 (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Form 941-Employer's Quarterly Federal Tax Return undated (Box-folder 37:11)
    - Form 990 2001-2002 (Box-folder 37:12)
    - Form 990 2002-2003 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Form 990 2003-2004 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Form 990 2004-2005 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - Grant Application - Norfolk Commission for the Arts and Humanities 2004-2005 (Box-folder 38:4)
    - Grant Application - Norfolk Commission for the Arts and Humanities 2005-2006 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - Grant Applications FY 2001-2002 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - Grant Applications FY 2003-2004 (Box-folder 38:7)
    - Grant Applications (I) FY 2004-2005 (Box-folder 38:8)
    - Grant Applications (II) FY 2004-2005 (Box-folder 38:9)
    - History of Grants 2000s (Box-folder 38:10)
    - Internal Audit 2003 (Box-folder 38:11)
    - Invoices - Morris Design 2004-2005 (Box-folder 38:12)
    - Kinkos Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2003-2004 (Box-folder 39:1)
    - Kinkos Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2004-2005 (Box-folder 39:2)
    - Kinkos Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2005-2006 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Misc. FY 2005-2006 (Box-folder 39:4)
    - Misc. Invoices 2005-2006 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Nation’s Bank Certificate File undated (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Office Max Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2004-2005 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - Pending Invoices 2005-2006 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Petty Cash Records 2004 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - Printing Invoices (2001-2004) (Box-folder 39:10)
    - Profit/Loss Report 2005-2006 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - Returned Checks 2005 (Box-folder 39:12)
    - Softmart Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2004-2005 (Box-folder 39:13)
    - Spectrum Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2003-2004 (Box-folder 39:14)
    - Spectrum Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2004-2005 (Box-folder 39:15)
    - Spectrum Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2005-2006 (Box-folder 40:1)
    - Supply Orders 2005-2006 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - Tax Form VA-5 2001 (Box-folder 40:3)
    - Tax Records 2001-2003 (Box-folder 40:4)
    - Temp Sheets- Image Services 2004-2005 (Box-folder 40:5)
    - Treasurer's Reports 1987- 2002 (Box-folder 40:6)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2000-2001 (Box-folder 40:7)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2001-2002 (Box-folder 40:8)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2002-2003 (Box-folder 40:9)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2002-2004 (Box-folder 40:10)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2003-2004 (Box-folder 40:11)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2004-2005 (Box-folder 40:12)
    - Treasurer's Reports 2005-2006 (Box-folder 40:13)
    - VA Beach Arts and Humanities Grant Application 2004-2005 (Box-folder 40:14)
    - VA Beach Arts and Humanities Grant Application 2005-2006 (Box-folder 40:15)
    - VA Foundation for the Humanities Grant Application 2005-2006 (Box-folder 40:16)
    - VDACS Form 102 2000-2001 (Box-folder 41:1)
    - VDACS Form 102 2001-2002 (Box-folder 41:2)
    - VDACS Form 102 2002-2003 (Box-folder 41:3)
    - VDACS Form 102 2003-2004 (Box-folder 41:4)
    - VDACS Form 102 2004-2005 (Box-folder 41:5)
    - VDACS Form 102 2005-2006 (Box-folder 41:6)
    - Venue/Catering Invoices/ Vendor Correspondence 2003-2005 (Box-folder 41:7)
    - Venue/Catering Invoices/ Vendor Correspondence 2004-2005 (Box-folder 41:8)
    - Venue/Catering Invoices/ Vendor Correspondence 2005-2006 (Box-folder 41:9)
    - Verizon Invoices/Vendor Correspondence 2003-2004 (Box-folder 41:10)
    - Virginia Beach Arts and Humanities Grant Information 2003-2004 (Box-folder 41:11)
    - Virginia Beach Arts and Humanities Grant Information 2004-2005 (Box-folder 41:12)
    - Virginia Beach Arts and Humanities Grant Information 2005-2006 (Box-folder 41:13)
    - Virginia Beach Foundation Grant Application 2001 (Box-folder 41:14)
    - Wachovia Investment Information 2003-2004 (Box-folder 41:15)
  - Publicity and Publications
    - News Releases / Newspaper Articles undated (Box-folder 41:16)
    - Newsletter - Vol. 5 2000-2001 (Box-folder 41:17)
    - Newsletter - Vol. 6 2002-2003 (Box-folder 41:18)
    - Newsletter - Vol. 7 2003-2004 (Box-folder 41:19)
    - Newsletter - Vol. 8 2004-2005 (Box-folder 41:20)
    - Newsletter - Vol. 9 2006 (Box-folder 41:21)
    - Publications undated (Box-folder 41:22)
    - Photos-Other Councils undated (Box-folder 41:23)
    - Newspaper Articles 2000-2004 (Box-folder 42:1)
    - Newsletters, WACA 2000-2004 (Box-folder 42:2)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Archives of WAC at ODU - Ray Taylor undated (Box-folder 42:3)
    - Certificates undated (Box-folder 42:4)
    - Floppy disks undated (Box-folder 42:5)
    - Foreign Consular Offices in Norfolk undated (Box-folder 42:6)
    - Logos undated (Box-folder 42:7)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 42:8)
    - Other Councils (I) undated (Box-folder 42:9)
    - Other Councils (II) undated (Box-folder 42:10)
    - Other Councils (III) undated (Box-folder 42:11)
    - Questionnaires (I) undated (Box-folder 43:1)
    - Questionnaires (II) undated (Box-folder 43:2)
    - Strategic Studies and Retreats undated (Box-folder 43:3)
  - Photos
    - Corporate Sponsor Campaign Lunch Photos 2001 (Box-folder 43:4)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs undated (Box-folder 43:5)
    - Negatives undated (Box-folder 43:6)
    - Office undated (Box-folder 43:7)
    - Photos - Speakers undated (Box-folder 43:8)
    - Waterside - Holiday Inn undated (Box-folder 43:9)
  - Oversize
    - Proclamation - World Affairs Council of Greater Hampton Roads Day undated (Box-folder 44:1)
    - Inside Business October 2-8, 2000 (Box-folder 44:2)
    - Inside Business June 28 - July 4, 2004 (Box-folder 44:3)